Guide to the Ladyslipper, Inc. Records, 1965-2011 and undated RL.10140
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials series, 1965-2009 and undated; 1
  - Althea Waites performs the Piano Music of Florence Price, 1987; 124
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0070)
  - Debbie Fier / Firelight, 1985; 125
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0071)
  - Jennifer Berezan / In the Eye of the Storm, 1988; 126
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0072)
  - The Neon Girls / Neonicity, 1995; 127
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0073)
  - Just Us Girls / Buffalo Gals, 1993; 128
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0074)
  - Disappear Fear / Echo My Call, 1988; 129
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0075)
  - Kay Gardner / Emerging, 1978; 130
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0076)
  - Comic Karen Ripley / Born Butch, 1998; 131
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0077)
  - Joanne Rand / Choosing Sides, 1989; 132
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0078)
  - Cathie Malach and Kim Rosen / Naked Waters, 1998; 133
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0079)
  - Eileen Edmonds, 1996; 134
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0080)
  - Ellen Hines / First Generation, 1992; 135
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0081)
  - Freeway Fusion / Textile, 1988; 136
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0082)
  - Kid Sister / Broken Bridges, 1995; 137
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0083)
  - D'Cuckoo / Umoja, 1994; 138
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0084)
  - Cat B'Lues / Lock'd In, 1998; 139
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0085)
  - Marion Weinstein / Stand-up Witch, 1989; 140
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0086)
  - Camp Song Favorites Sung by Pat Collins, undated; 141
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0087)
  - Hand in Hand: A Collection of Songs from the LeTs Bi Gay Community, undated; 142
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0088)
  - Walela, undated; 143
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0089)
  - Childman, 1993; 144
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0090)
  - Betty McDonald / Waltzing in the Sagebrush, 1995; 145
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0091)
  - Andrea Lyman / Return to Remember, 1991; 146
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0092)
  - United We Sing, tape 1, undated; 147
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0093)
  - United We Sing, tape 2, undated; 148
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0094)
  - Alix Dobkin and Friends / These Women Never Been Better, 1986; 149
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0095)
  - Deborah Martin and Steve Gordon / Ancient Power, 1998; 150
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0096)
  - K.D. Lang and the Reclines / Absolute Torch and Twang, 1989; 151
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0097)
  - Gabrielle Roth and the Mirrors / Zone Unknown, 1997; 152
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0098)
  - Liz Story / The Gift, 1994; 153
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0099)
  - Libby Roderick / Lay it All Down, 1997; 154
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0100)
  - Jamie Anderson / Center of Balance, 1992; 155
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0101)
  - Debbie Friedman / And You Shall Be a Blessing, 1989; 156
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0102)
  - Cris Williamson and Teresa Trull / Country Blessed, 1989; 157
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0103)
  - Jallen Rix / The Sacred and the Queer, 1995; 158
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0104)
  - Turtle Creek Chorale live / From the Heart, undated; 159
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0105)
  - Libby Roderick / Thinking Like a Mountain, 1991; 160
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0106)
  - Libby Roderick / If the World Were My Lover, 1993; 161
    - Original audiocassette (Box 73, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0107)
  - Holly Near and Ronnie Gilbert / Lifeline, 1988; 162
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0108)
  - Kay Gardner / Moods and Rituals, 1980; 163
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0109)
  - Nuru / Drum Call, 1993; 164
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0110)
  - Charlie Murphy and Jamie Sieber / Canticles of Light, 1984; 165
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0111)
  - 1st NWMF [National Women's Music Festival], 1974; 166
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0112)
  - 1975 National Women's Music Festival Highlights, 167
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0113)
  - Patchwork, 1982; 168
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0114)
  - unlabeled, undated; 169
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0115)
  - Rebecca Jane / Rainsong, 1984; 170
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0116)
  - Casselberry-Dupree [2 copies], undated; 171
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0117)
  - Koinonia talent nite- dining room- Bob, Ed, Mel, gospel sextet messing around /more serious Mel, Sam, Rach, Leah, Bob, undated; 172
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0118)
  - Koinonia talent night at white house- Bob, Mel, Sam, Kate here & dining room, undated; 173
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0119)
  - Julie Gold / The Official Demo Sessions, 1992; 174
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0120)
  - Can Dogs Talk?, undated; 175
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0121)
  - Lunacy, 1990; 176
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0122)
  - Together, Proud and Strong: Anthem for the 1993 March, 1992; 177
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0123)
  - The Bird Sisters / Flo, 1990; 178
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0124)
  - Cailleach / Ireland, undated; 179
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0125)
  - Para Laurie: Mujeres en Musica, 1983; 180
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0126)
  - Billie Holiday, Sally Oldfield, etc., undated; 181
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0127)
  - Rhiannon / Toward Home [2 copies], 1991; 182
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0128)
  - Casselberry-Dupree, undated; 183
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0129)
  - Batacoto, 1993; 184
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0130)
  - Teresa Trull / A Step Away, 1986; 185
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0131)
  - Fluke, undated; 186
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0132)
  - Rita Falbel / Timepieces: Between Jewish Past and Future, 1991; 187
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0133)
  - Susan Abod, 1985; 188
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0134)
  - Kay Gardner / Fishersdaughter, 1986; 189
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0135)
  - Ruth Barrett / Parthenogenesis, 1990; 190
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0136)
  - Sons & Lovers / a cappella, 1996; 191
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0137)
  - Tiye Giraud / hokumbe!, 1991; 192
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0138)
  - Diane Wolkstein and Geoffrey Gordon / The Epic of Inanna, 1983; 193
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0139)
  - Beth York / Transformations [2 copies], 1983; 194
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0140)
  - Ubaka Hill / Shapeshifters, undated; 195
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0141)
  - Beth Jochum and Brenda Fisher / Voices on the Wind, 1992; 196
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0142)
  - Earthworks / The Balance of Life, 1990; 197
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0143)
  - The New Age Movement, undated; 198
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0144)
  - Hagology / Queen of Wands, undated; 199
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0145)
  - NAIRS Distribs Crash Course, undated; 200
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0146)
  - Teresa Trull / A Step Away, 1986; 201
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0147)
  - Beverly Botsford / Demo- Works in Progress, 1995; 202
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0148)
  - Sunny McHale SkyeDancer / Lesbian Nation, 1991; 203
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0149)
  - Radience / Inverness, 1983; 204
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0150)
  - Venus Envy / Unarmed and Dangerous!, 1990; 205
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0151)
  - The MERE Project, 1992; 206
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0152)
  - Rachel Bagby / Grandmother's Song, 1993; 207
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0153)
  - Tsunami Records / Family of Friends, 1992; 208
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0154)
  - Wings / Women's History Month I and II, 1991; 209
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0155)
  - Earth on the Air / Vol. II, undated; 210
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0156)
  - Disappear Fear, 1992; 211
    - Original audiocassette (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0157)
  - Geof Morgan / It Comes with the Plumbing, 1980; 212
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0158)
  - Spiral Singers / Spinning Colors, 1996; 213
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0159)
  - Colibri / En el Lejano Bosque [In the Faraway Forest], undated; 214
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0160)
  - Christine Lavin / Good Thing He Can't Read my Mind, 1988; 215
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0161)
  - Anique / Lover Mine, 1994; 216
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0162)
  - Gaia / Our Childrens' World, undated; 217
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0163)
  - Thistle and Roses / Life's Minor Pleasures, 1992; 218
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0164)
  - Frances Black / Talk to Me, 1994; 219
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0165)
  - Boukman Eksperyans / Vodou Adjae, 1991; 220
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0166)
  - Robin Rose Bennett / Moon Meditations, 1998; 221
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0167)
  - Shri Ram / On Wings of Song & Robert Gass, 1991; 222
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0168)
  - Andy Freilich / Dragons, 1995; 223
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0169)
  - Kite / Talk to Me, undated; 224
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0170)
  - Deborah Franciose / Gypsy Heart, undated; 225
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0171)
  - Bonnie Rideout / Gi'me Elbow Room, 1998; 226
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0172)
  - The World Sings Goodnight, 1993; 227
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0173)
  - Peggy Monaghan / Seasons of the Witch, 1994; 228
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0174)
  - Femme M'amie / Song of Hands, 1994; 229
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0175)
  - Susan Nimue / Muffin's Story: An inner-active path to wholeness, 1991; 230
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0176)
  - The Ron Jones Project / Ionsca: Return to Passion, 1996; 231
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0177)
  - Ritual Motion / Feel It, 1995; 232
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0178)
  - Loreena McKennitt / To Drive the Cold Winter Away, 1994; 233
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0179)
  - Morgan and Phelan / Celebrations of Love, 1993; 234
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0180)
  - MT Chard / 267, 1998; 235
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0181)
  - Pendragon / Passage to New England, 1993; 236
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0182)
  - Black Girls / Happy, 1991; 237
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0183)
  - Ceili's Muse / Circles of Stone, 1993; 238
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0184)
  - Tariq / The Fire and the Rose, undated; 239
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0185)
  - Grace Nono / OPO, 1995; 240
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0186)
  - Brooke Medicine Eagle / Maiden, 1994; 241
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0187)
  - Teresa Trull and Barbara Higbie / Unexpected, 1983; 242
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0188)
  - Joemy Wilson / Gifts: Traditional Christmas Carols, 1985; 243
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0189)
  - Bonnie Rideout / Celtic Circles, 1994; 244
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0190)
  - Jane Field / The Fishing is Free, 1994; 245
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0191)
  - B'Kol Ishah: The Voice of Women Cantors, 1994; 246
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0192)
  - Feeding the Flame: Songs by Men to End AIDS, 1990; 247
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0193)
  - The Mother Folkers / Confluence, 1991; 248
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0194)
  - Jane and Julia / North Skye, 1992; 249
    - Original audiocassette (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0195)
  - 3rd NWMF, 1976; 250
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0196)
  - Holly Near and Ronnie Gilbert / Singing with You, 1986; 251
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0197)
  - Jezebel Moon / Premonition, 2000; 252
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0198)
  - Kath & Ini / Affirmations, 1985; 253
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0199)
  - Kristen Hall / Fact & Fiction, 1991; 254
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0200)
  - Girls in the Nose / Origin of the World, 1992; 255
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0201)
  - Girls in the Nose, 1990; 256
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0202)
  - A Family of Friends: Women's Music Sampler, 1993; 257
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0203)
  - Fem 2 Fem / Animus, 1995; 258
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0204)
  - Zenobia, 1994; 259
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0205)
  - Maria Therese Winter / EarthSong, 1991; 260
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0206)
  - Terry Garthwaite / Sacred Circles, 1999; 261
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0207)
  - Susan Herrick / Loving Me, 1991; 262
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0208)
  - Holly Near / Singer in the Storm, 1990; 263
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0209)
  - Capitol Steps / All I Want for Christmas is a Tax Increase, 1993; 264
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0210)
  - National Women's Music Festival Highlights, 1975; 265
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0211)
  - 1st NWMF [National Women's Music Festival], 1974; 266
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0212)
  - Rev. Delores P. Berry / This is Why I Sing, 1995; 267
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0213)
  - Icarus #2, 1974; 268
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0214)
  - Guardabarranco / Si Buscabas: If You Were Looking, 1985; 269
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0215)
  - Ferron / Still Riot, 1996; 270
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0216)
  - Ferron / Testimony, 1980; 271
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0217)
  - Meg Christian / Scrapbook, 1986; 272
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0218)
  - Kay Gardner / Echoes, undated; 273
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0219)
  - No Spring Chickens / Almost Commercially Viable, 1992; 274
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0220)
  - Casselberry-Dupree / City Down, 1987; 275
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0221)
  - Golden Bough / Winter's Dance, 1985; 276
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0222)
  - Casselberry-DuPree / Sister's Chant, the Klan, undated; 277
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0223)
  - Casselberry-DuPree, 1985; 278
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0224)
  - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival / Michigan Live '85 [sides 1 and 2], 1985; 279
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0225)
  - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival / Michigan Live '85 [sides 3 and 4], 1985; 280
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0226)
  - Ferron / Phantom Center, 1990; 281
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0227)
  - S3 Voice Ensemble / Together, Proud & Strong, 1992; 282
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0228)
  - Grayhawk / Blissful Magic: Spiral of the Celtic Mysteries, 1995; 283
    - Original audiocassette (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0229)
  - Kay Gardner / Sounding the Inner Landscape, 1990; 284
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0230)
  - Kay Gardner / A Rainbow Path, 1984; 285
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0231)
  - Constance Demby at Alaron, 1983; 286
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0232)
  - Disappear Fear / Echo My Call, 1988; 287
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0233)
  - Disappear Fear / Live at the Bottom Line, 1992; 288
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0234)
  - Sacred Circle / Living on the Wheel of the Year, undated; 289
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0235)
  - Violetta Parra / Cantos de Chile, 1979; 290
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0236)
  - Mim Dye / Spiritual Songs of Hildegard, 1993; 291
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0237)
  - Heather Bishop / A Taste of the Blues, 1987; 292
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0238)
  - The Best of Nina Simone, 1965; 293
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0239)
  - Betty / Limboland, 1995; 294
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0240)
  - Mary Black / Collected, 1984; 295
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0241)
  - Suede / Barely Blue, undated; 296
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0242)
  - Suede / Easily Suede, 1988; 297
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0243)
  - Kitka / Voices on the Eastern Wind, 1992; 298
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0244)
  - Doug Stevens & the Outband / Out in the Country, 1993; 299
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0245)
  - Indigo Girls / Shaming of the Sun, 1997; 300
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0246)
  - Kay Gardner and Nurudafina Pili Abena / OneSpirit, 1993; 301
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0247)
  - Kay Gardner and Sunwomyn Ensemble / Garden of Ecstasy, 1989; 302
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0248)
  - Kay Gardner / Moods and Rituals, 1980; 303
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0249)
  - Judy Small / Global Village, 1995; 304
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0250)
  - Sweet Honey in the Rock / In this Land, 1992; 305
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0251)
  - Ron Romanovsky / Hopeful Romantic, 1992; 306
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0252)
  - Lea DeLaria / Bulldyke in a China Shop, undated; 307
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0253)
  - Siren Song: A Celebration of Women in Music, 1996; 308
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0254)
  - Ann Reed / Back & Forth, undated; 309
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0255)
  - Saffire: The Uppity Blues Women, 1990; 310
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0256)
  - Saffire: The Uppity Blues Women / Hot Flash, 1991; 311
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0257)
  - Ruth Barret and Cynthia Smith / The Heart is the Only Nation, 1993; 312
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0258)
  - Faith Nolan / Freedom to Love, 1989; 313
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0259)
  - Koleet / A Celebration of Jewish Folk Music, undated; 314
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0260)
  - Debra Knodel and Jane Valencia / The Harper's Masque, 1992; 315
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0261)
  - Judy Small / The Best of the 80s, undated; 316
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0262)
  - God is My Co-Pilot / Straight Not, undated; 317
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0263)
  - Megha Shayla Dena / Water Ceremonial, 1991; 318
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0264)
  - Insane Jane / Each Finger, 1993; 319
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0265)
  - Heather Bishop / Walk That Edge, undated; 320
    - Original audiocassette (Box 117, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0266)